Guide to the R. Philip Hanes Papers, 1928-2010 RL.00503
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Ampersand Series: Casebooks, 1962?1987, 1977?1985
  - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art (SECCA), 1976-1982:
    - Contracts, Workplans, Questionnaire, 1976-1979 (Box 150)
    - Progress Reports, 1977-1981, 2 folders (Box 150)
    - Organizational Structure, 1962-1979 (Box 150)
  - SECCA, 1976-1982: (Box 151)
    - Organizational Structure, 1962-1979 (con't) (Box 151)
    - Organizational Development, 1974-1979, 4 folders (Box 151)
    - Marketing, 1976-1978 (Box 151)
  - SECCA, 1976-1982: (Box 152)
    - Marketing,1976-1979 (con't), 2 folders (Box 152)
    - Marketing: Events, 1976-1977 (Box 152)
  - SECCA, 1976-1982 (Box 153)
    - Marketing: Events, 1977-1979 (con't), 5 folders (Box 153)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 153)
  - SECCA, 1976-1982 (Box 154)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1979 (con't) (Box 154)
  - SECCA: Awards in the Visual Arts (AVA), 1979-1982
    - Contract, Workplan, Organizational Structure, Organizational Development, Marketing, 1980 (Box 154)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1981, 3 folders (Box 154)
    - Clippings and Publicity, 1979 (Box 154)
    - Contract, Progress Report, 1980 (Box 154)
    - AVA Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 154)
    - Other Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 154)
  - SECCA: AVA, 1979-1982 (Box 155)
    - General Correspondence, 1979-1981, 2 folders (Box 155)
    - Endorsements (Box 155)
    - Public Relations 1980, Mar.-Sept. (Box 155)
  - SECCA: AVA, 1979-1982 (Box 156)
    - Public Relations, 1980, Oct.-Dec. (Box 156)
    - Press Releases (Box 156)
    - Press Releases and Clippings, 1980 (Box 156)
    - Correspondence, 1981, 2 folders (Box 156)
    - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 156)
  - SECCA: Southeast 7 III, 1980 (Box 157)
    - Correspondence, 1982, 2 folders (Box 157)
    - Invitation List, 1980 (Box 157)
  - SECCA: Southeast 7 III, 1980 (Box 158)
    - Correspondence, 1980 and nd (Box 158)
    - Press Releases, 1980 (Box 158)
  - Southern Highlands Handicraft Guild (SHHG), 1974-1985
    - Contract, Workplan, Questionnaire, Progress Reports, 1974-1985 (Box 158)
    - Organizational Structure, 1977-1978 (Box 158)
    - Organizational Structure: Financials, 1975-1977 (Box 158)
    - Organizational Structure, Organizational Development, 1977-1979, 2 folders (Box 158)
    - Organizational Development: Grantsmanship, 1977-1979 (Box 158)
  - SHHG, 1974-1985 (Box 159)
    - Organizational Development: Grantsmanship, 1977-1979, 3 folders (Box 159)
  - SHHG, 1974-1985 (Box 160)
    - Organizational Development (con't) (Box 160)
    - Printed Material, Special Events (Box 160)
    - General Correspondence, 1976-1979, 2 folders (Box 160)
  - Spoleto Festival, 1983-1985
    - Chart of Phases, 1984-1985 (Box 160)
    - Special Events/Benefits, Fund Drive Updates, Spoleto Society, Board List, 1985 (Box 160)
    - Research, 1985 (Box 160)
  - Spoleto Festival, 1983-1985 (Box 161)
    - Research, 1985 (con't) (Box 161)
    - Direct Mail, 1985 (Box 161)
    - Gloria Theatre, 1984 (Box 161)
    - Budget, 1985, Prospects, Preliminary Research (Box 161)
    - Long Range Plan, 1985-1990 (Box 161)
  - Upstairs Gallery, 1984-1985
    - Contract, Financials, Public Relations, Program, Research, Correspondence, Report (Box 161)
  - Upstairs Gallery, 1984-1985 (Box 162)
    - Program Materials: Book Art/SE Touring Exhibit (Box 162)
    - Program Materials: Musical and Theatrical Performance (Box 162)
  - Walnut Street Theatre, 1982
    - Contract, Workplan, Questionnaire (Box 162)
    - Organizational Structure, 1978-1982, 3 folders (Box 162)
    - Organizational Development, 1980-1982 (Box 162)
  - Walnut Street Theatre, 1982 (Box 163)
    - Organizational Development, 1980-1982 (con't), 2 folders (Box 163)
    - Marketing, Public Relations, 1981-1982 (Box 163)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1982 (Box 163)
    - Other, 1982 (Box 163)
    - Short-Term Plan, 1982 (Box 163)
  - Winston-Salem Chamber of Commerce, 1981-1983
    - Tourism Data, 1981 (Box 163)
    - Tourism Task Force, 1983 (Box 163)
    - Press, 1982 (Box 163)
    - Economic Development Data, 1982 (Box 163)
  - Winston-Salem Chamber of Commerce, 1981-1983 (Box 164)
    - Chamber Internal Administration, 1982 (Box 164)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 164)
    - Seasons, 1983-1984 (Box 164)
  - Winston-Salem Downtown Revitalization, 1977-1982
    - Center City, 1978 (Box 164)
  - Cultural Block Concept Plan, 1977-1979
    - Cultural Action Plan (Box 164)
    - Cooperative Proposal for NEA Challenge Grant, 1978-1979, 4 folders (Box 164)
  - Winston-Salem Downtown Revitalization, 1977-1982 (Box 165)
    - Cooperative Proposal for NEA Challenge Grant, 1978-1979 (con't) (Box 165)
    - Center City Revitalization: Survey of 6 Cities, Representive Examples 1980, 2 folders (Box 165)
    - Cultural Block Plan Final Report, 1980, May (Box 165)
    - Local Media, National Media, 1978-1982 (Box 165)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1982, 3 folders (Box 165)
  - Winston-Salem Downtown Revitalization, 1977-1982 (Box 166)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1982 (con't) (Box 166)
  - Winston-Salem Symphony Association, 1983-1985
    - Long-Range Planning Material, Mission and Objectives, Programs, 1983-1985, 2 folders (Box 166)
    - Financials, 1983-1984 (Box 166)
    - Long-Range Plan: Interviews, 1984( 3 folders) (Box 166)
  - Winston-Salem Symphony Association, 1983-1985 (Box 167)
    - Long-Range Plan: ASOL Comparisons, Publicity (Box 167)
    - Fort Wayne Orchestra (Box 167)
    - Richmond Orchestra, Florida Orchestra (Box 167)
  - Winston-Salem Symphony Association, 1983-1985 (Box 168)
    - Other Symphonies and Art Councils, 1981-1985 (Box 168)
    - Richmond Symphony, 1981-1986 (Box 168)
    - Long-Range Planning Task Force, 1984, 3 folders (Box 168)
    - Long-Range Plan, 1984, 3 folders (Box 168)
  - Winston-Salem Symphony Association, 1983-1985 (Box 169)
    - Search Committee Information and Proceedures (Box 169)
    - Executive Search: General Manager, 1984 (Box 169)
    - Interviews (Box 169)
    - Long-Range Plan, Working Notebook and Interviews (Box 169)
    - Long-Range Plan, 3 folders (Box 169)
- Ampersand: Chronological Files, 1976?1985
  Office files of photocopied correspondence and memoranda, which also include a few proposals and reports for clients, lists (such as potential donors), and agreements and contracts. The letters are only copies of outgoing correspondence, mostly from Hanes, but some from other Ampersand staff. Originally this file was called the Green File because of the green paper photocopies. Chronological arrangement, with a folder or more for each month.
  - 1976, November 1-1977, March 17 (Box 170)
  - 1977, March 18-1977, July 13 (Box 171)
  - 1977, July 15-1977, October 31 (Box 172)
  - 1977, November 1-1978, February 14 (Box 173)
  - 1978, February 14-1978, April 28 (Box 174)
  - 1978, May 1-1978, July 31 (Box 175)
  - 1978, August 1-1978, November 15 (Box 176)
  - 1978, November 16-1979, February 8 (Box 177)
  - 1979, February 9-1979, April 30 (Box 178)
  - 1979, May 1-1979, July 31 (Box 179)
  - 1979, August 1-1979, October 30 (Box 180)
  - 1979, November 1-1980, February 28 (Box 181)
  - 1980, March 1-1980, June 17 (Box 182)
  - 1980, June 18-1980, October 15 (Box 183)
  - 1980, October 16-1981, March 10 (Box 184)
  - 1981, March 11-1981, June 15 (Box 185)
  - 1981, June 16-1981, September 16 (Box 186)
  - 1981, September 17-1981, December 31 (Box 187)
  - 1982, January 4-1982, April 21 (Box 188)
  - 1982, April 22-1982, May 28 (Box 189)
  - 1982, June 1-1982, August 31 (Box 190)
  - 1982, August-1982, November 30 (Box 191)
  - 1982, December 2-1983, March 14 (Box 192)
  - 1983, March 15-1983, April 13 (Box 193)
  - 1983, April 14 -1983, May 20 (Box 194)
  - 1983, May 23-1983, August 31 (Box 195)
  - 1983, September 1-1984, January 16 (Box 196)
  - 1984, January 17-1984, April 30 (Box 197)
  - 1984, May 1-1984, July 16 (Box 198)
  - 1984, July 17-1984, August 12 (Box 199)
  - 1984, August 13-1984, November 13 (Box 200)
  - 1984, November 14-1984, December 28 (Box 201)
  - 1985, January 2-1985, January (Box 202)
  - 1985, February 1-1985, March 15 (Box 203)
  - 1985, March 16-1985, April 14 (Box 204)
  - 1985, April 15-1985, August 19 (Box 205)
  - 1985, August 20-October 31 (Box 206)
  - 1985, November 4-1986, March 14, 3 folders (Box 207)
- Ampersand: Central Files, 1976?1985
  Chiefly office files of photocopied letters and memoranda as well as some other mimeographed and printed material and clippings. The correspondence is primarily outgoing, with some original copies of incoming letters. There is a separate grouping for each one or two-year period, with topical folders arranged in an alphabetical sequence for each year or years. Included are general folders for a single letter of the alphabet as well as specific names of organizations and topics. Many of the folders are thin; early files tend to be the largest.
  - 1976?1977
    - (A)
      - Aging and the Arts (Box 207)
      - American Crafts Council: Correspondence (Box 207)
      - American Crafts Council: Information (Box 207)
      - American Crafts Council: Meetings (Box 207)
      - Ampersand Creative Problem Solving Workship, 1977, August (Box 207)
      - Art Park: Correspondence (Box 207)
      - Associated Councils of the Arts: Correspondence (Box 207)
      - Associated Councils of the Arts: Information (Box 207)
      - Associated Councils of the Arts: Meetings (Box 207)
      - Associated Councils of the Arts: 1977 Questionnaire (Box 207)
      - Association for Community Cooperation: Correspondence (Box 207)
      - Association for Community Cooperation: Information (Box 208)
    - (B)
      - Brakeley, John Price Jones, Inc.: Correspondence (Box 208)
      - Business Committee for the Arts (Box 208)
      - Business Committee for the Arts Award (Box 208)
      - Business Committee for the Arts: Correspondence (Box 208)
      - Business Committee for the Arts: Informaiton (Box 208)
    - (C)
      - Carter, Jimmy: Correspondence (Box 208)
      - Carter, Jimmy: Information (Box 208)
      - Carter, Jimmy: Press (Box 208)
      - Client Information, 1977 (Box 208)
      - Consulting Organizations: General Information (Box 208)
      - Consulting Organizations: General: Information (Box 209)
      - Council on Foundations: Arts Survey (Box 209)
      - Council on Foundations: Correspondence (Box 209)
      - Council on Foundations: Information (Box 209)
      - Council on Foundations: Meetings (Box 209)
      - Council on Foundations: 17th Annual Conference/ May 11-14, 1976 (Box 209)
      - Crafts (Box 209)
    - (D)
      - Davenport, Tom: Correspondence (Box 209)
      - Dept. of Administration: Correspondence (Box 209)
      - Dept. of Administration: Grants (Box 209)
      - Dept. of Administration: Information (Box 209)
      - Dept. of Archives and History: Correspondence (Box 209)
      - Dept. of Commerce: Correspondence (Box 209)
      - Dept. of Cultural Resources: Correspondence (Box 209)
      - Dept. of Health, Education, and Welfare: Correspondence (Box 210)
      - Dept. of the Interior: Correspondence (Box 210)
      - Duke University (Box 210)
    - (E)
      - Education: NCSU Seminar (Box 210)
    - (F)
      - Federal Reserve Board, 1977 (Box 210)
      - Friends of Univeristy Network Television: Correspondence (Box 210)
      - Foundation Center: Correspondence (Box 210)
    - (G) (Box 210)
    - (H)
      - Hunt, Jim: Correspondence (Box 210)
      - Hunt, Jim: Information (Box 210)
      - Hunt, Jim: Press (Box 210)
    - (I) (Box 210)
    - (J) (Box 210)
    - (K) (Box 210)
    - (L)
      - L. Richardson Hospital (Box 210)
    - (M)
      - Mondale, Walter (Box 210)
      - Museums/Galleries: Correspondence (Box 210)
      - Medical Center: Correspondence (Box 210)
      - Moravian Music Foundation: Correspondence (Box 210)
      - Moravian Music Foundation: Memoranda (Box 210)
      - Moravian Music Foundation: Press (Box 210)
      - Museum of Early Southern Decorative Arts: Correspondence (Box 210)
      - Museum of Early Southern Decorative Arts: Memoranda (Box 210)
      - Museums/Galleries: Information (Box 210)
    - (N)
      - National Association for the Southern Poor: Correspondence (Box 211)
      - National Association for the Southern Poor: Information (Box 211)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities: Correspondence (Box 211)
      - The National Rural Center: Correspondence (Box 211)
      - The National Rural Center: Information (Box 211)
      - The National Rural Center: Press (Box 211)
      - North Carolina: Correspondence (Box 211)
      - North Carolina: Information (Box 211)
      - North Carolina Arts Council: Correspondence (Box 211)
      - North Carolina Dance Theater (Box 211)
      - North Carolina Museum of Art: Correspondence (Box 211)
      - North Carolin Museum of Art: Information (Box 211)
      - North Carolina School of the Arts: Correspondence (Box 211)
      - North Carolina School of the Arts: Contract (Box 211)
      - North Carolina School of the Arts: Press (Box 211)
      - North Carolina Symphony: Correspondence (Box 211)
      - North Carolina Theater Ensembel (Box 211)
      - Northwest Economic Development Commission: Information (Box 211)
      - Northwest North Carolina Development Association: Information (Box 211)
    - (O)
      - Old Salem: Correspondence and Press (Box 211)
    - (P)
      - Piedmont Carftsmen: Correspondence (Box 211)
      - Piedmont Craftsmen: Information (Box 211)
      - Piedmont Craftsmen: Memoranda (Box 211)
      - Piedmont Craftsmen: Press (Box 211)
      - Pine Island, 1977 (Box 211)
      - Politics-Federal: General Correspondence (Box 211)
      - Press (Box 212)
      - Public Interest Public Relations: Information (Box 212)
    - (Q) (Box 212)
    - (R)
      - R. J. Reynolds (Box 212)
      - Ruder and Finn: Correspondence (Box 212)
    - (S)
      - Salem College: Correspondence (Box 212)
      - The South: Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 212)
      - The South: Memoranda (Box 212)
      - The South: Press (Box 212)
      - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art, April Opening, April 1-3, 1977: Attendees (Box 212)
      - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art, April Opening, April 1-3, 1977: Correspondence (Box 212)
      - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art, April Opening, April 1-3, 1977: Hunt Dinner Speech (Box 212)
      - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art: Correspondence (Box 212)
      - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art: Grants (Box 212)
      - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art: Information (Box 212)
      - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art: Press (Box 212)
      - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art: Southeastern Art Collectors (Box 212)
      - Southeastern Council of Foundations: Correspondence (Box 212)
      - Southeastern Council of Foundations: Foundation Forum/September 12-13, 1975 Organizations--Reference (Box 212)
      - Southeastern Council of Foundations: Information (Box 213)
      - Southeastern Council of Foundations: 6th Annual Meeting/November 5-7, 1975 (Box 213)
      - Southeastern Council of Foundations: 7th Annual Meeting/October 20-22, 1977 (Box 213)
      - Southern Federation of State: Arts Agencies (Box 213)
      - Southern Highland Handicraft Guild: Correspondence (Box 213)
      - Southern Highland Handicraft Guild: Information (Box 213)
    - (T)
      - Taft, Inc.: Correspondence (Box 213)
    - (U) (Box 213)
    - (V) (Box 213)
    - (W)
      - Winston-Salem: W-S apprentices (Box 213)
      - Winston-Salem: Arts--Listing of Arts in City (Box 213)
      - Winston-Salem: Fund Raising (Box 213)
      - Winston-Salem: General (Box 213)
      - Winston-Salem: Information Sheet--NEA 8 (Box 213)
      - Winston-Salem: Tour (Box 213)
      - Winston-Salem Arts Council: Challenge Grant, 2 folders (Box 213)
      - Winston-Salem Arts Council: "R-70" Correspondence (Box 213)
      - Winston-Salem Arts Council: Correspondence (Box 213)
      - Winston-Salem Arts Council: Information (Box 213)
      - Winston-Salem Arts Council: JDR III (Box 214)
      - Winston-Salem Arts Council: Memoranda (Box 214)
      - Winston-Salem Arts Council: Press (Box 214)
      - Winston-Salem Arts Council: Proposals (Box 214)
      - Winston-Salem Chamber of Commerce: Correspondence (Box 214)
      - Winston-Salem Chamber of Commerce: Memoranda (Box 214)
      - Winston-Salem Redevelopment: Correspondence (Box 214)
      - Winston-Salem Redevelopment: Information (Box 214)
      - Winston-Salem Redevelopment: Press (Box 214)
      - Winston-Salem Redevelopment: Proposals (Box 214)
      - Winston-Salem Redevelopment: Ralph Burgard Letter (Box 214)
      - Winston-Salem School System: Correspondence (Box 214)
      - Winston-Salem State University: Correspondence (Box 214)
      - Wachovia Bank, 1977 (Box 214)
      - Wake Forest: Correspondence (Box 214)
    - (Y) (Box 214)
    - (Z) (Box 214)
  - 1978
    - (A)
      - American Dance Festival (Box 214)
      - American Council for the Arts (Box 214)
      - Ampersand Creative Problem Solving Workshop (Box 215)
      - The Arts (Box 215)
      - Arts Business Publications (Box 215)
    - (B)
      - Business Committee for the Arts: Award (Box 215)
      - Business Committee for the Arts: General (Box 215)
      - Business Committee for the Arts: News (Box 215)
    - (C)
      - Carter, Jimmy and Rosalyn (Box 215)
      - Center for Creative Leadership (Box 215)
      - Clearinghouse for Midcontinent Foundations (Box 215)
      - Council on Foundations: General (Box 216)
      - Council Foundations: Memorandum (Box 216)
      - Consulting Organizations (Box 216)
    - (D)
      - Davenport, Tom (Box 216)
      - Department of Commerce (Box 216)
      - N.C. Department of Commerce (Box 216)
      - Department of Cultural Resources (Box 216)
      - Department of Health, Education and Welfare (Box 216)
      - Department of Interior (Box 216)
      - Duke University (Box 216)
    - (E) (Box 216)
    - (F)
      - Foundation Center (Box 216)
    - (G) (Box 216)
    - (H)
      - Hunt, Jim (Box 216)
    - (I)
      - International Communication Agency (Box 216)
    - (J) (Box 216)
    - (K) (Box 216)
    - (L) (Box 217)
    - (M)
      - Mondale, Walter and Joan (Box 217)
      - Museum of Ceramic Art (Box 217)
      - Museum Services (Box 217)
      - Museums/Galleries (Box 217)
    - (N)
      - National Association for the Southern Poor (Box 217)
      - National Citizens Communications Lobby (Box 217)
      - National Endowment for the Arts: Government-Federal, 3 folders (Box 217)
      - NEA: Prior Grants (Box 217)
      - NEA: Prior Grants (Box 218)
      - New TransCentury Foundation: Challenge Grants (Box 218)
      - North Carolina (Box 218)
      - N.C. Arts Council (Box 218)
      - N.C. Symphony (Box 218)
      - Northwest Environmental Preservation Committee (Box 218)
    - (O) (Box 218)
    - (P)
      - Phoenix Organization (Box 218)
    - (R) (Box 219)
    - (S)
      - Salem College (Box 219)
      - Southeastern Council of Foundations (Box 219)
      - Senators/Representatives (Box 219)
      - Southern Foundation of State Arts Agencies (Box 219)
      - Symphonies (Box 219)
    - (T)
      - Theatres (Box 219)
    - (U) (Box 219)
    - (V) (Box 219)
    - (W)
      - Wachovia Bank (Box 219)
      - Wake Forest University (Box 219)
      - Winston-Salem: Arts Council Exhibits A-G (Box 219)
      - Winston-Salem: Chamber of Commerce (Box 219)
      - Winston-Salem: Coliseum Downtown (Box 219)
      - Winston-Salem: Development Plan: Steering Committee (Box 219)
      - Winston-Salem: Downtown Redevelopment (Box 219)
      - Winston-Salem: General (Box 219)
      - Winston-Salem: Integon (Box 219)
      - Winston-Salem: R. J. Reynolds (Box 219)
      - Winston-Salem: R. J. Reynolds Proposal (Box 219)
      - Winston-Salem: R. J. Reynolds (Box 220)
      - Winston-Salem: Redevelopment (Box 220)
      - Winston-Salem: School System (Box 220)
      - Winston-Salem State University (Box 220)
    - (X, Y, Z) (Box 220)
  - 1979
    - (A)
      - American Council for the Arts (Box 220)
      - Ampersand Memos (Box 220)
      - Ampersand Staff Memos (Box 220)
    - (B)
      - Black Mountain College (Box 220)
      - Business Committee for the Arts (Box 220)
    - (C)
      - Council on Foundations (Box 220)
    - (D) (Box 221)
      - Department of Administration (Box 221)
      - Department of Archives and History (Box 221)
      - Department of Commerce (Box 221)
      - Department of Cultural Resources (Box 221)
      - Department of Housing and Urban Development (Box 221)
      - Department of Interior (Box 221)
      - Duke University (Box 221)
    - (E) (Box 221)
    - (F) (Box 221)
    - (G) (Box 221)
    - (H)
      - Hunt, Jim (Box 221)
    - (I)
      - International Communication Agency (Box 221)
    - (J) (Box 221)
    - (K) (Box 221)
    - (L) (Box 221)
    - (M) (Box 222)
      - Mondale (Box 222)
    - (N)
      - NEA (Box 222)
    - (O) (Box 222)
    - (P)
      - Press (Box 222)
    - (Q) (Box 222)
    - (R) (Box 222)
    - (S)
      - Salem College (Box 222)
      - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies, 2 folders (Box 222)
      - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies (Box 223)
      - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies: Boston (Box 223)
      - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies: Vienna Checks (Box 223)
      - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies: Vienna Opera (Box 223)
      - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies: Vienna Responses (Box 224)
      - Senators (Box 224)
      - Southeastern Council of Foundations (Box 224)
    - (T) (Box 224)
    - (U) (Box 224)
    - (V) (Box 224)
    - (W)
      - Winston-Salem: Downtown (Box 224)
      - Winston-Salem: Wake Forest (Box 224)
      - Winston-Salem: Chamber of Commerce (Box 224)
      - Winston-Salem: Coliseum Downtown (Box 224)
      - Winston-Salem: Reynolds (Box 224)
      - Winston-Salem: School System (Box 224)
      - Winston-Salem: Wachovia (Box 224)
      - Winston-Salem and Forsyth County: Cultural Action Plan (Box 224)
      - Winston-Salem Development Plan: Steering Committee, 2 folders (Box 224)
      - Winston-Salem State University (Box 224)
    - (Y) (Box 224)
  - 1980
    - (A)
      - American Council for the Arts (Box 224)
      - Ampersand (Box 225)
    - (B) (Box 225)
    - (C)
      - Carter, Jimmy (Box 225)
      - Corporate Contributions (Box 225)
    - (D) (Box 225)
    - (E) (Box 225)
    - (F)
      - Feinstein, Martin (Box 225)
    - (G) (Box 225)
    - (H)
      - Hunt, Jim (Box 225)
    - (I)
      - International Communications Agency (Box 225)
    - (K) (Box 225)
    - (L) (Box 225)
    - (M)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 225)
      - Mondale, Walter and Joan (Box 225)
    - (N)
      - NEA (Box 225)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities (Box 225)
      - New World Foundation (Box 225)
      - North Carolina: General Information (Box 225)
      - N.C. Arts Council (Box 225)
    - (O) (Box 225)
    - (P)
      - Partnership Opportunities Conference (Box 225)
      - Peirce, Neal R. (Box 225)
      - Press (Box 226)
    - (R) (Box 226)
    - (S)
      - SC-ETV Network (Box 226)
      - Salem College (Box 226)
      - Senators/Representatives (Box 226)
      - SE Council on Foundations (Box 226)
    - (T) (Box 226)
    - (W)
      - Winston-Salem: Chamber of Commerce (Box 226)
      - Winston-Salem: Coliseum Downtown (Box 226)
      - Winston-Salem and Forsyth County: Center City Development Guide (Box 226)
      - Winston-Salem and Forsyth County: Cultural Action Plan (Box 226)
      - Winston-Salem: R. J. Reynolds (Box 226)
      - Winston-Salem: Wachovia (Box 226)
      - Winston-Salem Development Plan: Steering Committee (Box 226)
    - (Y) (Box 226)
    - (Z) (Box 226)
  - 1981
    - (A)